🎵 Goodness of God (선하신 주) - 찬양 전주
Goodness of God - Bethel Music (Intro)
[1절] 사랑합니다 주님, 주의 자비는 결코 날 떠나지 않네
I love You, Lord, Oh, Your mercy never failed me
내 모든 날 동안 주의 손에 붙들렸네
All my days, I've been held in Your hands
내가 눈뜰 때부터 잠자리에 들 때까지, 주의 선하심을 노래하리라
From the moment that I wake up until I lay my head, Oh, I will sing of the goodness of God
[후렴] 내 평생 주님은 언제나 신실하셨고
And all my life You have been faithful
내 평생 주님은 참으로 선하셨네
And all my life You have been so, so good
내 호흡이 다하는 그 순간까지, 주의 선하심을 노래하리라
With every breath that I am able, Oh, I will sing of the goodness of God
[2절] 주님의 음성을 사랑합니다, 불 가운데로 날 인도하셨네
I love Your voice, You have led me through the fire
가장 어두운 밤에도 누구보다 가까이 계셨네
And in darkest night You are close like no other
나의 아버지, 나의 친구 되신 주, 나 주의 선하심 안에 살아가리
I've known You as a Father, I've known You as a Friend, and I have lived in the goodness of God
[후렴] 내 평생 주님은 신실하셨고
And all my life You have been faithful
내 평생 주님은 참으로 선하셨네
And all my life You have been so, so good
내 호흡이 다하도록 주의 선하심을 노래하리라
With every breath that I am able, Oh, I will sing of the goodness of God
[브릿지] 주의 선하심이 나를 따르네, 날마다 나를 따르네
'Cause Your goodness is running after, it's running after me
내 삶을 주께 드리며 온전히 순종하오니 주께 모든 것 드립니다
With my life laid down, I'm surrendered now, I give You everything
[브릿지 절정] 주의 선하심이 나를 따르네, 끊임없이 나를 따르네!
'Cause Your goodness is running after, it keeps running after me!
[후렴 절정] 내 평생 주님은 신실하셨네, 주의 선하심을 영원히 찬양하리라
All my life You have been faithful, I will sing of the goodness of God
🕊️ 평생토록 신실하신 주님의 선하심에 감사드립니다 · 아멘
Forever Thankful for the Goodness of God · Amen